<prayers><prayer title="Medium Obligatory Prayer" citation="" author="Bahá’u’lláh" category="Obligatory">&lt;p class="commentcaps">To be recited daily, in the morning, at noon, and in the evening.&lt;/p>

&lt;p class="comment">Whoso wisheth to pray, let him wash his hands, and while he washeth, let him say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Strengthen my hand, O my God, that it may take hold of Thy Book with such steadfastness that the hosts of the world shall have no power over it.  Guard it, then, from meddling with whatsoever doth not belong unto it.  Thou art, verily, the Almighty, the Most Powerful.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">And while washing his face, let him say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>I have turned my face unto Thee, O my Lord! Illumine it with the light of Thy countenance.  Protect it, then, from turning to anyone but Thee.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Then let him stand up, and facing the Qiblih (Point of Adoration, i.e., Bahjí, ‘Akká), let him say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>God testifieth that there is none other God but Him.  His are the kingdoms of Revelation and of creation.  He, in truth, hath manifested Him Who is the Dayspring of Revelation, Who conversed on Sinai, through Whom the Supreme Horizon hath been made to shine, and the Lote-Tree beyond which there is no passing hath spoken, and through Whom the call hath been proclaimed unto all who are in heaven and on earth: “Lo, the All-Possessing is come.  Earth and heaven, glory and dominion are God's, the Lord of all men, and the Possesser of the Throne on high and of earth below!”&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him, then, bend down, with hands resting on the knees, and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Exalted art Thou above my praise and the praise of anyone beside me, above my description and the description of all who are in heaven and all who are on earth!&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Then, standing with open hands, palms upward toward the face, let him say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Disappoint not, O my God, him that hath, with beseeching fingers, clung to the hem of Thy mercy and Thy grace, O Thou Who of those who show mercy art the Most Merciful!&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him, then, be seated and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>I bear witness to Thy unity and Thy oneness, and that Thou art God, and that there is none other God beside Thee.  Thou hast, verily, revealed Thy Cause, fulfilled Thy Covenant, and opened wide the door of Thy grace to all that dwell in heaven and on earth.  Blessing and peace, salutation and glory, rest upon Thy loved ones, whom the changes and chances of the world have not deterred from turning unto Thee, and who have given their all, in the hope of obtaining that which is with Thee.  Thou art, in truth, the Ever-Forgiving, the All-Bountiful.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">(If anyone choose to recite instead of the long verse these words: “God testifieth that there is none other God but Him, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting,” it would be sufficient.  And likewise, it would suffice were he, while seated, to choose to recite these words: “I bear witness to Thy unity and Thy oneness, and that Thou art God, and that there is none other God beside Thee.”)&lt;p>

 



</prayer><prayer title="Short Obligatory Prayer" citation="" author="Bahá’u’lláh" category="Obligatory">&lt;p class="commentcaps">To be recited once in twenty four hours, at noon.&lt;p>

&lt;p>I bear witness, O my God, that Thou hast created me to know Thee and to worship Thee.  I testify, at this moment, to my powerlessness and to Thy might, to my poverty and to Thy wealth.&lt;p>

&lt;p>There is none other God but Thee, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting.&lt;p></prayer><prayer title="Long Obligatory Prayer" citation="" author="Bahá’u’lláh" category="Obligatory">&lt;p class="commentcaps">To be recited once in twenty-four hours.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Whoso wisheth to recite this prayer, let him stand up and turn unto God and, as he standeth in his place, let him gaze to the right and to the left, as if awaiting the mercy of his Lord, the Most Merciful, the Compassionate. Then let him say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>O Thou Who art the Lord of all names and the Maker of the heavens!  I beseech Thee by them Who are the Day-Springs of Thine invisible Essence, the Most Exalted, the All-Glorious, to make of my prayer a fire that will burn away the veils which have shut me out from Thy beauty, and a light that will lead me unto the ocean of Thy Presence.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then raise his hands in supplication toward God—blessed and exalted be he—and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>O Thou the Desire of the world and the Beloved of the nations!  Thou seest me turning toward Thee, and rid of all attachment to any one save Thee, and clinging to Thy cord, through whose movement the whole creation hath been stirred up.  I am Thy servant, O my Lord, and the son of Thy servant.  Behold me standing ready to do Thy will and Thy desire, and wishing naught else except Thy good pleasure.  I implore Thee by the Ocean of Thy mercy and the Daystar of Thy grace to do with Thy servant as Thou willest and pleasest.  By Thy might which is far above all mention and praise!  Whatsoever is revealed by Thee is the desire of my heart and the beloved of my soul.  O God, my God!  Look not upon my hopes and my doings, nay rather look upon Thy will that hath encompassed the heavens and the earth.  By Thy Most Great Name, O Thou Lord of all nations!  I have desired only what Thou didst desire, and love only what Thou dost love.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then kneel, and bowing his forehead to the ground, let him say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Exalted art Thou above the description of any one save Thyself, and the comprehension of aught else except Thee.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then stand and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Make my prayer, O my Lord, a fountain of living waters whereby I may live as long as Thy sovereignty endureth, and may make mention of Thee in every world of Thy worlds.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him again raise his hands in supplication, and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>O Thou in separation from Whom hearts and souls have melted, and by the fire of Whose love the whole world hath been set aflame!  I implore Thee by Thy Name through which Thou hast subdued the whole creation, not to withhold from me that which is with Thee, O Thou Who rulest over all men!  Thou seest, O my Lord, this stranger hastening to his most exalted home beneath the canopy of Thy majesty and within the precincts of Thy mercy; and this transgressor seeking the ocean of Thy forgiveness; and this lowly one the court of Thy glory; and this poor creature the orient of Thy wealth.  Thine is the authority to command whatsoever Thou willest.  I bear witness that Thou art to be praised in Thy doings, and to be obeyed in Thy behests, and to remain unconstrained in Thy bidding.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then raise his hands, and repeat three times the Greatest Name (“Alláh-u-Abhá”).  Let him then bend down with hands resting on the knees before God—blessed and exalted be He—and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Thou seest, O my God, how my spirit hath been stirred up within my limbs and members, in its longing to worship Thee, and in its yearning to remember Thee and extol Thee; how it testifieth to that whereunto the tongue of Thy Commandment hath testified in the kingdom of Thine utterance and the heaven of Thy knowledge.  I love in this state, O my Lord, to beg of Thee all that is with Thee, that I may demonstrate my poverty, and magnify Thy bounty and Thy riches, and may declare my powerlessness, and manifest Thy power and Thy might.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then stand and raise his hands twice in supplication, and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>There is no God but Thee, the Almighty, the All-Bountiful.  There is no God but Thee, the Ordainer, both in the beginning and in the end.  O God, my God!  Thy forgiveness hath emboldened me, and Thy mercy hath strengthened me and Thy call hath awakened me, and Thy grace hath raised me up and led me unto Thee.  Who, otherwise, am I that I should dare to stand at the gate of the city of Thy nearness, or set my face toward the lights that are shining from the heaven of Thy will?  Thou seest, O my Lord, this wretched creature knocking at the door of Thy grace, and this evanescent soul seeking the river of everlasting life from the hands of Thy bounty.  Thine is the command at all times, O Thou Who art the Lord of all names; and mine is resignation and willing submission to Thy will, O Creator of the heavens! &lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then raise his hands thrice, and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Greater is God than every great one!&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then kneel, and bowing his forehead to the ground, say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Too high art Thou for the praise of those who are nigh unto Thee to ascend unto the heaven of Thy nearness, or for the birds of the hearts of them who are devoted to Thee to attain to the door of Thy gate.  I testify that Thou hast been sanctified above all attributes and holy above all names.  No God is there but Thee, the Most Exalted, the All-Glorious.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then seat himself and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>I testify unto that whereunto have testified all created things, and the Concourse on high, and the inmates of the all-highest Paradise, and beyond them the Tongue of Grandeur itself from the all-glorious Horizon, that Thou art God, that there is no God but Thee, and that He Who hath been manifested is the Hidden Mystery, the Treasured Symbol, through Whom the letters B and E (Be) have been joined and knit together.  I testify that it is He Whose name hath been set down by the Pen of the Most High, and Who hath been mentioned in the Books of God, the Lord of the Throne on high and of earth below.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then stand erect and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>O Lord of all being and Possessor of all things visible and invisible!  Thou dost perceive my tears and the sighs I utter, and hearest my groaning, and my wailing, and the lamentation of my heart.  By Thy might!  My trespasses have kept me back from drawing nigh unto Thee; and my sins have held me far from the court of Thy holiness.  Thy love, O my Lord, hath enriched me, and separation from Thee hath destroyed me, and remoteness from Thee hath consumed me.  I entreat Thee by Thy footsteps in this wilderness, and by the words “Here am I. Here am I” which Thy chosen Ones have uttered in this immensity, and by the breaths of Thy Revelation, and the gentle winds of the Dawn of thy Manifestation, to ordain that I may gaze on Thy beauty and observe whatsoever is in Thy Book.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then repeat the Greatest Name thrice, and bend down with hands resting on the knees, and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Praise be to Thee, O my God, that Thou hast aided me to remember Thee and to praise Thee, and hast made known unto me Him Who is the Dayspring of Thy signs, and hast caused me to bow down before Thy Lordship, and humble myself before Thy Godhead, and to acknowledge that which hath been uttered by the Tongue of Thy grandeur.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then rise and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>O God, my God!  My back is bowed by the burden of my sins, and my heedlessness hath destroyed me.  Whenever I ponder my evil doings and Thy benevolence, my heart melteth within me, and my blood boileth in my veins.  By Thy Beauty, O Thou the Desire of the world!  I blush to lift up my face to Thee, and my longing hands are ashamed to stretch forth toward the heaven of Thy bounty.  Thou seest, O my God, how my tears prevent me from remembering Thee and from extolling Thy virtues, O Thou the Lord of the Throne on high and of earth below!  I implore Thee by the signs of Thy Kingdom and the mysteries of Thy Dominion to do with Thy loved ones as becometh Thy bounty, O Lord of all being, and is worthy of Thy grace, O King of the seen and the unseen! &lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then repeat the Greatest Name thrice, and kneel with his forehead to the ground, and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>Praise be unto Thee, O our God, that Thou has sent down unto us that which draweth us nigh unto Thee, and supplieth us with every good thing sent down by Thee in thy Books and thy Scriptures.  Protect us, we beseech Thee, O my Lord, from the hosts of idle fancies and vain imaginations.  Thou, in truth, art the Mighty, the All-Knowing.&lt;p>

&lt;p class="comment">Let him then raise his head, and seat himself, and say:&lt;p>

&lt;p>I testify, O my God, to that whereunto Thy chosen Ones have testified, and acknowledge that which the inmates of the all-highest Paradise and those who have circled round Thy mighty Throne have acknowledged.  The kingdoms of earth and heaven are Thine, O Lord of the worlds!&lt;p>

</prayer><prayer title="&quot;O Thou Whose face is the object...&quot;" citation="" author="Bahá’u’lláh" category="Assistance">&lt;P>O Thou Whose face is the object of my adoration, Whose beauty is my sanctuary, Whose habitation is my goal, Whose praise is my hope, Whose providence is my companion, Whose love is the cause of my being, Whose mention is my solace, Whose nearness is my desire, Whose presence is my dearest wish and highest aspiration, I entreat Thee not to withhold from me the things Thou didst ordain for the chosen ones among Thy servants.  Supply me, then, with the good of this world and of the next.&lt;P>

&lt;P>Thou, truly, art the King of all men.  There is no God but Thee, the Ever-Forgiving, the Most Generous.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;My God, my Adored One, my King...&quot;" citation="" author="Bahá’u’lláh" category="Assistance">&lt;P>My God, my Adored One, my King, my Desire!  What tongue can voice my thanks to Thee?  I was heedless, Thou didst awaken me.  I had turned back from Thee, Thou didst graciously aid me to turn towards Thee.  I was as one dead, Thou didst quicken me with the water of life.  I was withered, Thou didst revive me with the heavenly stream of Thine utterance which hath flowed forth from the Pen of the All-Merciful.&lt;P>

&lt;P>O Divine Providence!  All existence is begotten by Thy bounty; deprive it not of the waters of Thy generosity, neither do Thou withhold it from the ocean of Thy mercy.  I beseech Thee to aid and assist me at all times and under all conditions, and seek from the heaven of Thy grace Thine ancient favor.  Thou art, in truth, the Lord of bounty, and the Sovereign of the kingdom of eternity.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;Lauded be Thy Name, O Lord our God!&quot;" citation="" author="The Báb" category="Assistance">&lt;P>Lauded be Thy Name, O Lord our God!  Thou art in truth the Knower of things unseen.  Ordain for us such good as Thine all-embracing knowledge can measure.  Thou art the sovereign Lord, the Almighty, the Best-Beloved.&lt;P>

&lt;P>All praise be unto Thee, O Lord!  We shall seek Thy grace on the appointed Day and shall put our whole reliance in Thee, Who art our Lord.  Glorified art Thou, O God!  Grant us that which is good and seemly that we may be able to dispense with everything but Thee.  Verily, Thou art the Lord of all worlds.&lt;P>

&lt;P>O God!  Recompense those who endure patiently in Thy days, and strengthen their hearts to walk undeviatingly in the path of Truth.  Grant then, O Lord, such goodly gifts as would enable them to gain admittance into Thy blissful Paradise.  Exalted art Thou, O Lord God.  Let Thy heavenly blessings descend upon homes whose inmates have believed in Thee.  Verily, unsurpassed art Thou in sending down divine blessings.  Send forth, O God, such hosts as would render Thy faithful servants victorious.  Thou dost fashion the created things through the power of Thy decree as Thou pleasest.  Thou art in truth the Sovereign, the Creator, the All-Wise.&lt;P>

&lt;P>Say: God is indeed the Maker of all things.  He giveth sustenance in plenty to whomsoever He willeth.  He is the Creator, the Source of all beings, the Fashioner, the Almighty, the Maker, the All-Wise.  He is the Bearer of the most excellent titles throughout the heavens and the earth and whatever lieth between them.  All do His bidding, and all the dwellers of earth and heaven celebrate His praise, and unto Him shall all return.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="O my God, my Lord and my Master!" citation="" author="The Báb" category="Assistance">&lt;P>O my God, my Lord and my Master!  I have detached myself from my kindred and have sought through Thee to become independent of all that dwell on earth and ever ready to receive that which is praiseworthy in Thy sight.  Bestow on me such good as will make me independent of aught else but Thee, and grant me an ampler share of Thy boundless favors.  Thou art the Lord of grace abounding.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;Lord! Pitiful are we, grant us Thy favor...&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Assistance">&lt;P>Lord!  Pitiful are we, grant us Thy favor; poor, bestow upon us a share from the ocean of Thy wealth; needy, do Thou satisfy us; abased, give us Thy glory.  The fowls of the air and the beasts of the field receive their meat each day from Thee and all beings partake of Thy care and loving kindness.&lt;P>

&lt;P>Deprive not this feeble one of Thy wondrous grace and vouchsafe by Thy might unto this helpless soul Thy bounty.&lt;P>

&lt;P>Give us our daily bread and grant Thy increase in the necessities of life, that we may be dependent on none other than Thee, may walk in Thy ways and declare Thy mysteries.  Thou art the Almighty and the Loving and the Provider of all mankind.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O Thou kind Lord! We are servants...&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Assistance">&lt;P>O Thou kind Lord!  We are servants of Thy Threshold, taking shelter at Thy holy Door.  We seek no refuge save only this strong pillar, turn nowhere for a haven but unto Thy safekeeping.  Protect us, bless us, support us, make us such that we shall love but Thy good pleasure, utter only Thy praise, follow only the pathway of truth, that we may become rich enough to dispense with all save Thee, and receive our gifts from the sea of Thy beneficence, that we may ever strive to exalt Thy Cause and to spread Thy sweet savors far and wide, that we may become oblivious of self and occupied only with Thee, and disown all else and be caught up in Thee. &lt;P>

&lt;P>O Thou Provider, O Thou Forgiver!  Grant us Thy grace and loving-kindness, Thy gifts and Thy bestowals, and sustain us, that we may attain our goal.  Thou art the Powerful, the Able, the Knower, the Seer; and, verily, Thou art the Generous, and, verily, Thou art the All-Merciful, and, verily, Thou art the Ever-Forgiving, He to Whom repentance is due, He Who forgiveth even the most grievous of sins.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;Remove not, O Lord, the festal board...&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Assistance">&lt;P>Remove not, O Lord, the festal board that hath been spread in Thy Name, and extinguish not the burning flame that hath been kindled by Thine unquenchable fire.  Withhold not from flowing that living water of Thine that murmureth with the melody of Thy glory and Thy remembrance, and deprive not Thy servants from the fragrance of Thy sweet savors breathing forth the perfume of Thy love. &lt;P>

&lt;P>Lord!  Turn the distressing cares of Thy holy ones into ease, their hardship into comfort, their abasement into glory, their sorrow into blissful joy, O Thou that holdest in Thy grasp the reins of all mankind!&lt;P>

&lt;P>Thou art, verily, the One, the Single, the Mighty, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="O Thou kind Lord!" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="America">&lt;P>O Thou kind Lord!  This gathering is turning to Thee.  These hearts are radiant with Thy love.  These minds and spirits are exhilarated by the message of Thy glad-tidings.  O God!  Let this American democracy become glorious in spiritual degrees even as it has aspired to material degrees, and render this just government victorious.  Confirm this revered nation to upraise the standard of the oneness of humanity, to promulgate the Most Great Peace, to become thereby most glorious and praiseworthy among all the nations of the world.  O God!  This American nation is worthy of Thy favors and is deserving of Thy mercy.  Make it precious and near to Thee through Thy bounty and bestowal.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="Bless Thou, O King of Kings, the city of New York!" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="America">&lt;P>Bless Thou, O King of Kings, the city of New York!  Cause the friends there to be kind to one another.  Purify their souls and make their hearts to be free and detached.  Illumine the world of their consciousness.  Exhilarate their spirits and bestow celestial power and confirmation upon them.  Establish there a heavenly realm, so that the City of Baha may prosper and New York be favoured with blessings from the Abha Kingdom, that this region may become like the all-highest Paradise, may develop into a vineyard of God and be transformed into a heavenly orchard and a spiritual rose garden.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="Mother Temple of the West" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="America">&lt;P>O God, my God!  I implore Thee with a throbbing heart and streaming tears to aid whosoever expendeth his energy for the erection of this House, and the construction of this Building wherein Thy name is mentioned every morn and every eve.&lt;P>

&lt;P>O God!  Send down Thy divine increase on whosoever endeavoreth to serve this edifice and exerteth himself to raise it amongst the kindreds and religions of the world.  Confirm him in every good deed in promoting the welfare of mankind.  Open Thou the doors of wealth and abundance unto him and make him an heir to the treasures of the Kingdom, which perish not.  Make him a sign of Thy bestowals among the peoples and reinforce him by the sea of Thy generosity and bounty, surging with waves of Thy grace and favor.  Verily, Thou art the Generous, the Merciful and the Bountiful.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O Lord, my God! This is a child...&quot;" citation="" author="Bahá’u’lláh" category="Children">&lt;P>O Lord, my God!  This is a child that hath sprung from the loins of one of Thy servants to whom Thou hast granted a distinguished station in the Tablets of Thine irrevocable decree in the Books of Thy behest.&lt;P>

&lt;P>I beseech Thee by Thy name, whereby everyone is enabled to attain the object of his desire, to grant that this child may become a more mature soul amongst Thy servants; cause him to shine forth through the power of Thy name, enable him to utter Thy praise, to set his face towards Thee and to draw nigh unto Thee.  Verily it is Thou Who hast, from everlasting, been powerful to do as Thou willest and Who wilt, to eternity, remain potent to do as Thou pleasest.  There is none other God but Thee, the Exalted, the August, the Subduer, the Mighty, the All-Compelling.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O God! Educate these children.&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>O God!  Educate these children.  These children are the plants of Thine orchard, the flowers of Thy meadow, the roses of Thy garden.  Let Thy rain fall upon them; let the Sun of Reality shine upon them with Thy love.  Let Thy breeze refresh them in order that they may be trained, grow and develop, and appear in the utmost beauty.  Thou art the Giver.  Thou art the Compassionate.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O Thou kind Lord!&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>O Thou kind Lord!  These lovely children are the handiwork of the fingers of Thy might and the wondrous signs of Thy greatness.  O God!  Protect these children, graciously assist them to be educated and enable them to render service to the world of humanity.  O God!  These children are pearls, cause them to be nurtured within the shell of Thy loving-kindness. &lt;P>

&lt;P>Thou art the Bountiful, the All-Loving.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="O Lord! Make these children excellent plants." citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>O Lord!  Make these children excellent plants.  Let them grow and develop in the Garden of Thy Covenant, and bestow freshness and beauty through the outpourings from the clouds of the all-glorious Kingdom.&lt;P>

&lt;P>O Thou kind Lord!  I am a little child, exalt me by admitting me to the kingdom.  I am earthly, make me heavenly; I am of the world below, let me belong to the realm above; gloomy, suffer me to become radiant; material, make me spiritual, and grant that I may manifest Thine infinite bounties.&lt;P>

&lt;P>Thou art the Powerful, the All-Loving.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="He is God! O God, my God!" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>He is God!  O God, my God!  Bestow upon me a pure heart, like unto a pearl.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O God, guide me, protect me...&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>O God, guide me, protect me, make of me a shining lamp and a brilliant star.  Thou art the Mighty and the Powerful.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O my Lord! O my Lord!&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>O my Lord!  O my Lord!&lt;P>

&lt;P>I am a child of tender years.  Nourish me from the breast of Thy mercy, train me in the bosom of Thy love, educate me in the school of Thy guidance and develop me under the shadow of Thy bounty.  Deliver me from darkness, make me a brilliant light; free me from unhappiness, make me a flower of the rose garden; suffer me to become a servant of Thy threshold and confer upon me the disposition and nature of the righteous; make me a cause of bounty to the human world, and crown my head with the diadem of eternal life.&lt;P>

&lt;P>Verily, Thou art the Powerful, the Mighty, the Seer, the Hearer.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O Peerless Lord!&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>O Peerless Lord!  Be Thou a shelter for this poor child and a kind and forgiving Master unto this erring and unhappy soul.  O Lord!  Though we are but worthless plants, yet we belong to Thy garden of roses.  Though saplings without leaves and blossoms, yet we are a part of Thine orchard.  Nurture this plant then through the outpourings of the clouds of Thy tender mercy and quicken and refresh this sapling through the reviving breath of Thy spiritual springtime.  Suffer him to become heedful, discerning and noble, and grant that he may attain eternal life and abide in Thy Kingdom for evermore.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O my God! O my God!&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>O my God!  O my God!  Thou seest these children who are the twigs of the tree of life, the birds of the meads of salvation, the pearls of the ocean of Thy grace, the roses of the garden of Thy guidance.&lt;P>

&lt;P>O God, our Lord!  We sing Thy praise, bear witness to Thy sanctity and implore fervently the heaven of Thy mercy to make us lights of guidance, stars shining above the horizons of eternal glory amongst mankind, and to teach us a knowledge which proceedeth from Thee.  Yá Bahá’u’l-Abhá!&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O Lord! I am a child...&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>O Lord!  I am a child; enable me to grow beneath the shadow of Thy loving-kindness.  I am a tender plant; cause me to be nurtured through the outpourings of the clouds of Thy bounty.  I am a sapling of the garden of love; make me into a fruitful tree.&lt;P>

&lt;P>Thou art the Mighty and the Powerful, and Thou art the All-Loving, the All-Knowing, the All-Seeing.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O Thou most glorious Lord!&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="Children">&lt;P>O Thou most glorious Lord!  Make this little maidservant of Thine blessed and happy; cause her to be cherished at the threshold of Thy oneness, and let her drink deep from the cup of Thy love so that she may be filled with rapture and ecstasy and diffuse sweet-smelling fragrance.  Thou art the Mighty and the Powerful, and Thou art the All-Knowing, the All-Seeing.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God!&quot;" citation="" author="Bahá’u’lláh" category="The Departed">&lt;P>Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God!  Abase not him whom Thou hast exalted through the power of Thine everlasting sovereignty, and remove not far from Thee him whom Thou hast caused to enter the tabernacle of Thine eternity.  Wilt Thou cast away, O my God, him whom Thou hast overshadowed with Thy Lordship, and wilt Thou turn away from Thee, O my Desire, him to whom Thou hast been a refuge?  Canst Thou degrade him whom Thou hast uplifted, or forget him whom Thou didst enable to remember Thee?&lt;P>

&lt;P>Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God!  Abase not him whom Thou hast exalted through the power of Thine everlasting sovereignty, and remove not far from Thee him whom Thou hast caused to enter the tabernacle of Thine eternity.  Wilt Thou cast away, O my God, him whom Thou hast overshadowed with Thy Lordship, and wilt Thou turn away from Thee, O my Desire, him to whom Thou hast been a refuge?  Canst Thou degrade him whom Thou hast uplifted, or forget him whom Thou didst enable to remember Thee? &lt;P>

&lt;P>Glorified, immeasurably glorified art Thou!  Thou art adored in Thy truth, and Thee do we all, verily, worship; and Thou art manifest in Thy justice, and to thee do we all, verily, bear witness.  Thou art, in truth, beloved in Thy grace.  No God is there but Thee, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;He is God, exalted is He...&quot;" citation="" author="Bahá’u’lláh" category="The Departed">&lt;P>He is God, exalted is He, the Lord of loving-kindness and bounty!&lt;P>

&lt;P>Glory be unto Thee, Thou, O my God, the Lord Omnipotent.  I testify to Thine Omnipotence and Thy might, Thy sovereignty and Thy loving-kindness, Thy grace and Thy power, the oneness of Thy being and the unity of Thine Essence, Thy sanctity and exaltation above the world of being and all that is therein.&lt;P>

&lt;P>O my God!  Thou seest me detached from all save Thee, holding fast unto Thee and turning unto the ocean of Thy bounty, to the heaven of Thy favor, to the Daystar of Thy grace.&lt;P>

&lt;P>Lord!  I bear witness that in Thy servant Thou hast reposed Thy Trust, and that is the Spirit wherewith Thou hast given life to the world.&lt;P>

&lt;P>I ask of Thee by the splendor of the Orb of Thy Revelation, mercifully to accept from him that which he hath achieved in Thy days.  Grant then that he may be invested with the glory of Thy good-pleasure and adorned with Thine acceptance.&lt;P>

&lt;P>O my Lord!  I myself and all created things bear witness unto Thy might, and I pray Thee not to turn away from Thyself this spirit that hath ascended unto Thee, unto Thy heavenly place, Thine exalted Paradise and Thy retreats of nearness, O Thou who art the Lord of all men!&lt;P>

&lt;P>Grant, then, O my God, that Thy servant may consort with Thy chosen ones, Thy saints and Thy Messengers in heavenly places that the pen cannot tell nor the tongue recount.&lt;P>

&lt;P>O My Lord, the poor one hath verily hastened unto the Kingdom of Thy wealth, the stranger unto his home within Thy precincts, he that is sore athirst to the heavenly river of Thy bounty.  Deprive him not, O Lord, from his share of the banquet of Thy grace and from the favor of Thy bounty.  Thou art in truth the Almighty, the Gracious, the All-Bountiful.&lt;P>

&lt;P>O my God, Thy Trust hath been returned unto Thee.  It behooveth Thy grace and Thy bounty that have compassed Thy dominions on earth and in heaven, to vouchsafe unto Thy newly welcomed one Thy gifts and Thy bestowals, and the fruits of the tree of Thy grace!  Powerful art Thou to do as Thou willest, there is none other God but Thee, the Gracious, the Most Bountiful, the Compassionate, the Bestower, the Pardoner, the Precious, the All-Knowing.&lt;P>

&lt;P>I testify, O my Lord, that Thou hast enjoined upon men to honor their guest, and he that hath ascended unto Thee hath verily reached Thee and attained Thy Presence.  Deal with him then according to Thy grace and bounty!  By Thy glory, I know of a certainty that Thou wilt not withhold Thyself from that which Thou hast commanded Thy servants, nor wilt Thou deprive him that hath clung to the cord of Thy bounty and hath ascended to the Dayspring of Thy wealth.&lt;P>

&lt;P>There is none other God but Thee, the One, the Single, the Powerful, the Omniscient, the Bountiful.&lt;P></prayer><prayer title="&quot;O my God! O Thou forgiver of sins...&quot;" citation="" author="'Abdu’l-Bahá" category="The Departed"></prayer></prayers>